that a
send
loot
[music]
hello
hello friends i am vishram and you are watching
my channel workshop good so ah
as in front of you or apache 4v black
as you can see this vehicle's tank
is completely broken
and the axle is also damaged going ahead
you can see this the right side candle
bar is scratched the axle is also slightly broken from the side
this is your full tank cover disc
is fitted you can see below there is leg guard
and in front of it you can see the
right side of the light ola fauji
aquestion is
ah just look at the look of the other how is it
banked
now let's take it inside and do
its dismantling and we will
also do the boxer process inside you all are welcome to
our channel if you
like to watch videos related to vehicles then
subscribe to our channel so that
you can get notifications when we release
and those who wish our in-laws a big
thank you Jai Hind Jai
Ho
[music]
that last skirt let's start this entry
but first of all we will
remove its axle because its axle is completely
banked  It is done, which has to be cut out and taken out.
We have looked very carefully, it will come out
from here, carefully we have
cut it completely in half from the bottom, still it is
very strong because it is not coming out from one side,
now we are taking it out from the front side,
but it has to be taken out and cutting is the
only way, we cut it gently, from here and there,
cutting from all sides slowly, it is
not taken out, how much time does it take, how is it done like this,
question is, how long does it take to cut
it, finally we decided to
put it on the scooter from the bottom and
cut it in one go, let's see if it is damaged
or not, so
finally it is finished,
what can I see,
it has been cut out very well, it is
not damaged anywhere here or there, it is only where there is damage, there is
no damage anywhere here or there, so we
cut it out properly, we do this
process of taking out this oil,
after that we will see and
[Music]
I don't keep it from here, do it, it has happened, it has been an
irony of do it friends, because
after the treatment is complete, we are going to tell
which reader  I have got it for repair but it is not
found and which parts are damaged and how much is it
because this is a new car because when the car is
not new then
companies accept even a slight scratch, so
see which patches in it are
accepted as plane, then stay tuned to the video, it has happened
[music] it has happened
[music] it has
happened [music] it has happened
[music] it has happened
[music] it is working for
[music] give me the
phone number here it has happened [music] it has happened
[music] it has happened
[music] it is working for [
music]
I have
already dismantled the car, let me
show you it is 4th edition it has
happened do it,
rock band it has happened,
whose alignment will be done, there is no
problem, but the alignment will be done
and the
customer's service,
I have to send it late today, the
author is worried about the fat one
and this cold one  It has been broken into
two pieces, there is
more show
and in this friend and it seems scared, A
[Music] that
see this is the condition of the action, that's why we have been able to take out this
fast
[Music] by
cutting it with something and explaining
this mixture had become different,
this is a packet of difference, in this it is fourth class, he is
telling him to change it in a well
planned manner, if it is fine then it is fine,
otherwise he will have to change it, right
side amla field under cover use, I have to
question the handle also, it is a
little tied in the handle, if
I will not keep it here then it has happened, when it has
rotted, it is raised here,
I will give you in the dividend history chapter,
this is your foot like the life, this one is of the life, I have to
question and clear light from the plate, at
a
time,
Dara, put a little Sanskrit, Ahmed, watch this, the
video of Delhi Police will be made, it will come in the throat, so
if you have not subscribed to the channel then
please click so that you can get the notification right now
and thank you very much for watching the video and if you
liked the video then like it and if you have
any opinion about the video
So please write in the comment box,
thank you once again, Jai Hind, Jai Bhairav,
save life on
Jhal
[Music]
Kar Do